No nudity. No violence. Unspeakable obscenity.
The Aristocrats is a comedy, documentary film directed by Paul Provenza.
One hundred superstar comedians tell the same very, VERY dirty, filthy
joke--one shared privately by comics since Vaudeville.
Self, played by Jason Alexander.
Self - HBO Chairman / CEO, played by Chris Albrecht.
Self, played by Hank Azaria.
Self, played by Shelley Berman.
Billy the Mime (as Billy the Mime), played by Steven Gary Banks.
Self, played by Lewis Black.
The Aristocrats is a 2005 American documentary comedy
film about the famous eponymous dirty joke.
The film was conceived and produced by comedians Penn Jillette, Paul
Provenza and Peter Adam Golden, and it was edited by Emery Emery.
Distributed by THINKFilm, it is dedicated to Johnny Carson, as
"The Aristocrats" was said to be his favorite joke.
The film explores themes of aftercreditsstinger,
duringcreditsstinger, shaggy dog story.
The tone is lighthearted.